var questionList = [
    { 
        question: "Besides their exuberance and raw power, what other attribute did the band possess that 'knocked out' film maker Martin DiBergi?",
        answers: ["Musicianship", "Tardiness", "Responsibility", "Punctuality"],
        correctAns: 3
    },
    { 
        question: "During the fall of 1982, Spinal Tap embarked on a US tour to support the release of their new album. What was the title of this album?",
        answers: ["Firing on all Six", "Ride the Lightning", "Smell the Glove", "The Number of the Beast"],
        correctAns: 2
    },
    { 
        question: "On the band's arrival at JFK airport they were to be picked up and driven into the city. What was written on the sign being held by their chauffeur?",
        answers: ["Spinal Rap", "Vinyl Crap", "Urinal Tap", "Spinal Pap"],
        correctAns: 3
    },
    { 
        question: "Prior to calling themselves Spinal Tap, the band, which was founded during 1964, were known as The Originals. Over time they settled on a name relevant to the city in which the band was founded. What name had they finally opted for?",
        answers: ["Kings of Leon", "The Starland Vocal Band", "The Banana Splits", "The Thamesmen"],
        correctAns: 3
    },
    { 
        question: "The band revealed during an interview that their original drummer, John 'Stumpy' Pepys had died in a bizarre gardening incident. In which manner did his replacement, Eric 'Stumpy Joe' Childs, meet his demise?",
        answers: ["He drowned in a bath of baked beans", "He choked on vomit...somebody else's!", "Through a party game involving an explosion.", "During an amorous encounter with a sexy dwarf."],
        correctAns: 1
    },
    { 
        question: "During an inspection of Nigel Tufnel's amazing collection of guitars and equipment, Martin DiBergi was warned not to touch, or even look at, a specific brand of guitar. Which brand of guitar was this?",
        answers: ["Gretsch", "Gibson", "Fender", "Jackson"],
        correctAns: 2
    },
    { 
        question: "Before the show at the Vandermint Auditorium in Chapel Hill NC, Nigel Tufnel was experiencing particular difficulties with what in the band's dressing room?",
        answers: ["Groupies", "Spare guitar strings", "Spandex trousers", "The food"],
        correctAns: 3
    },
    { 
        question: "An equipment malfunction at the Shank Hall, Milwaukee WI concert results in band member Derek Smalls being trapped inside which of the following stage props?",
        answers: ["A steel cage", "A translucent chrysalis-like container", "An enormous bean-bag", "A large net"],
        correctAns: 1
    },
    { 
        question: "Which item did band manager Ian Faith carry with him at all times, which was described by DiBergi as an 'affectation' and by Faith himself as 'a kind of totemistic thing y'know'?",
        answers: ["His girlfriend's underwear", "A brightly coloured satchel", "A cricket bat", "A pair of his mother's ear-rings"],
        correctAns: 2
    },
    { 
        question: "At the Xanadu Star Theatre concert in Cleveland OH, what is it that delays the band's appearance on-stage and which results in a near riot?",
        answers: ["Their vehicle suffers a breakdown.", "The band get lost on the way to the stage.", "Their tour bus is stolen from outside the previous venue.", "A fire destroys all of their instruments."],
        correctAns: 1
    },
    { 
        question: "The use of a replica of an ancient monument found at a European UNESCO World Heritage site results in the band being mocked on stage by the audience after its use as a stage prop. Which important historical landmark was this?",
        answers: ["Nelson's Column", "The Giant's Causeway", "The Angel of the North", "Stonehenge"],
        correctAns: 3
    },
    { 
        question: "After the arrival during the tour of St. Hubbins' girlfriend Jeanine Pettibone, she attempted to give each member of the band a new on-stage persona. Which sign of the zodiac did she envisage Derek Smalls as?",
        answers: ["Virgo", "Sagittarius", "Cancer", "Aquarius"],
        correctAns: 2
    },
    { 
        question: "After Nigel Tufnel stormed off stage at the Air Force base concert, the band lost their direction. They were booked to play a gig at the Themeland Amusement Park, Stockton CA, but on arrival were disappointed to see on the billboard that they have been billed after which form of children's entertainment?",
        answers: ["A ventriloquist", "A troupe of clowns", "A mime artiste", "A puppet show"],
        correctAns: 3
    }

    
]